Soren|"Oy! Breya, hand me the wrench! The brass piping is coming loose on the furnace's exhaust."|0|R
Breya|"Oh! Uh... Here it is Mr. Soren."|1|L
Soren|"Ah, finally done! This baby will be keeping someone warm for the winter."|0|R
Soren|"Now, what were you trying to tell me earlier?"|0|R
Breya|"I was just reminding you that I’m leaving work early today. Emilia and I are planning on going scavenging tonight."|1|L
Soren|"Hmph right. You did put in extra work yesterday… Very well. How long until you leave?"|0|R
Breya|"I still have about two hours."|1|L
Soren|"Then help me patch up this exhaust vent until then. Its hinges have come loose."|0|R
Breya|"Yes sir!"|1|L